A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Offices xFA116
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Field Offices - New Delhi, India, 1960-1978, undated; 7; 4.4 Cubic Feet 11 document cases
  - Indian Agricultural Program - Crop Improvement Programs, 1955-1973, n.d.; I4; 57 __Boxes __21.4 cubic feet
    - Indian Agricultural Program - Crop Improvement Programs - Maize, 1957-1972; I4.01
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Kalimpong and Kalyani, West Bengal, 1957-1968 (Box 42, Folder 287)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Punjab, 1957-1970 (Box 42, Folder 288)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize experiment stations - Punjab, 1957-1970 (Box 42, Folder 289)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Punjab, 1957-1970 (Box 42, Folder 290)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Pusa, Bihar, 1961-1969 (Box 42, Folder 291)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Pusa, Bihar, 1961-1969 (Box 42, Folder 292)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Srinagar - General, 1957-1970 (Box 43, Folder 293)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Srinagar - General, 1957-1970 (Box 43, Folder 294)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Srinagar - Equipment, 1957-1971 (Box 43, Folder 295)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Srinagar - Equipment, 1957-1971 (Box 43, Folder 296)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Tabiji, Rajasthan - General, 1957-1964 (Box 43, Folder 297)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Tabiji, Rajasthan - General, 1957-1964 (Box 43, Folder 298)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Tabiji, Rajasthan - Equipment, 1957-1971 (Box 43, Folder 299)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Tabiji, Rajasthan - Equipment, 1957-1971 (Box 43, Folder 300)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Tarai, Upau, 1957-1967 (Box 43, Folder 301)
      - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Maize Experiment Stations - Tarai, Upau, 1957-1967 (Box 43, Folder 302)
      - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 303)
      - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 304)
      - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 305)
      - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 306)
      - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 307)
      - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 308)
      - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 309)
      - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 310)
      - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - General, 1963-1973 (Box 44, Folder 311)
      - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University, Pantnagar, 1964-1973 (Box 45, Folder 312)
      - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University, Pantnagar, 1964-1973 (Box 45, Folder 313)
      - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Administrative Correspondence - Uttar Pradesh Agricultural University, Pantnagar, 1964-1973 (Box 45, Folder 314)
      - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Maize Diseases - Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 45, Folder 315)
      - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Scholarships - Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 45, Folder 316)
      - Maize International Program - Cambodia, 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 317)
      - Maize International Program - Indonesia, 1962-1964 (Box 45, Folder 318)
      - Maize International Program - Malaysia, 1962-1964 (Box 45, Folder 319)
      - Maize International Program - Sri Lanka, 1962-1964 (Box 45, Folder 320)
      - Maize International Program - Thailand, 1961-1966 (Box 45, Folder 321)
      - Maize International Program - Thailand, 1967-1971 (Box 46, Folder 322)
      - Maize International Program - Vietnam, 1963-1964 (Box 46, Folder 323)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - Grant, U. J. and Wellhausen, E. J., "A Study of Corn Breeding and Production in India", 1955 (Box 46, Folder 324)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - Sprague, Ernest W., "Research to Improve Production of Corn in Asia", 1963 (Box 46, Folder 0324a)
      - Reports (Printed) - All India Coordinated Maize Improvement Scheme (AICMIS) - Pedigrees of Experimental Hybrids, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 325)
      - Reports (Printed) - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Progress Report, 1969-1970; 2 volumes (Box 46, Folder 326)
      - Reports (Printed) - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) - Summary Report, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 327)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Agricultural Research Institute (IARI) - Proceedings of the All India Maize Improvement Conference, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 328)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Annual Report, 1964-1966 (Box 46, Folder 329)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Annual Report, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 330)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Proceedings of the Maize Conference, 1962 (Box 47, Folder 331)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1958-1961 (Box 47, Folder 332)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1958-1961 (Box 47, Folder 333)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1958-1961 (Box 47, Folder 334)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1958-1961 (Box 47, Folder 335)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 336)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 337)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 338)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 339)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1964-1966 (Box 49, Folder 340)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1964-1966 (Box 49, Folder 341)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1964-1966 (Box 49, Folder 342)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1964-1966 (Box 49, Folder 343)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 344)
      - Reports (Printed) - Indian Council of Agricultural Research (ICAR) - Progress Report, 1971-1972 (Box 50, Folder 345)
    - Indian Agricultural Program - Crop Improvement Programs - Millet (All India Coordinated Millet Improvement Program), 1965-1972; I4.02
      Correspondence relating to the establishment and organization of the millet program appears first within this subseries. Correspondence of a miscellaneous character follows, treating such technical matters as experiment station operations, equipment maintenance, conference and workshop scheduling, training programs, relations with other agricultural organizations, and research programs in seed collection, breeding, entomology and pathology.
      Correspondence is typically followed by unpublished and published reports summarizing the results of experimental tests. These reports are arranged alphabetically by title. Filed with unpublished reports are manuscript drafts of reports on various aspects of the research programs. Also present are "trip reports" written by staff from the field.
      - Correspondence, 1965-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 346)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 347)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 348)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1968, 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 349)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1964-1968 (Box 51, Folder 350)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1964-1968 (Box 51, Folder 351)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1964-1968 (Box 51, Folder 352)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1964-1968 (Box 51, Folder 353)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1968-1971 (Box 52, Folder 354)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1968-1971 (Box 52, Folder 355)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1968-1971 (Box 52, Folder 356)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 357)
    - Indian Agricultural Program - Crop Improvement Programs - Rice (All India Coordinated Rice Improvement Project), 1964-1973; I4.03
      Correspondence relating to the establishment and organization of the rice program appears first within Subseries 3. Correspondence of a miscellaneous character follows, treating such technical matters as experiment station operations, equipment maintenance, conference and workshop scheduling, training programs, relations with other agricultural organizations, and research programs in seed collection, breeding, entomology and pathology.
      Correspondence is typically followed by unpublished and published reports summarizing the results of experimental tests. These reports are arranged alphabetically by title. Filed with unpublished reports are manuscript drafts of reports on various aspects of the research programs. Also present are "trip reports" written by staff from the field. Subseries 3 contains the trip reports of Wayne H. Freeman (1968-1973).
      - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 358)
      - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 359)
      - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 360)
      - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 361)
      - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 362)
      - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 363)
      - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 364)
      - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 365)
      - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1964-1970 (Box 54, Folder 366)
      - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1971-1973 (Box 55, Folder 367)
      - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1971-1973 (Box 55, Folder 368)
      - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1971-1973 (Box 55, Folder 369)
      - Correspondence - Administration and Organization, 1971-1973 (Box 55, Folder 370)
      - Correspondence - Cooperative Investigations, 1966-1967 (Box 56, Folder 371)
      - Correspondence - Cooperative Investigations, 1966-1967 (Box 56, Folder 372)
      - Correspondence - Foreign Rice Workers (Visiting), 1966-1968 (Box 56, Folder 373)
      - Correspondence - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - General, 1967-1973 (Box 56, Folder 374)
      - Correspondence - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - General, 1967-1973 (Box 56, Folder 375)
      - Correspondence - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - Draft Agreement with Indian Council of Agricultural Research, 1970-1973 (Box 56, Folder 376)
      - Correspondence - Rice Agronomy, 1966-1969 (Box 56, Folder 377)
      - Correspondence - Rice Diseases, 1967-1970 (Box 56, Folder 378)
      - Correspondence - Rice Seed Samples, 1965-1971 (Box 56, Folder 379)
      - Correspondence - Treflan (Rice Weedicide), 1970 (Box 57, Folder 380)
      - Project Summaries and Statistics, 1967-1973 (Box 57, Folder 381)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - Reports of Wayne H. Freeman, 1968-1973 (Box 57, Folder 382)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - Reports of Wayne H. Freeman, 1968-1973 (Box 57, Folder 383)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - Reports of Wayne H. Freeman, 1968-1973 (Box 57, Folder 384)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - Reports of Wayne H. Freeman, 1968-1973 (Box 57, Folder 385)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - IRRI/USAID Quarterly Reports, 1967-1972 (Box 57, Folder 386)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1965-1967 (Box 58, Folder 387)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1965-1967 (Box 58, Folder 388)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1965-1967 (Box 58, Folder 389)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1965-1967 (Box 58, Folder 390)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1965-1967 (Box 58, Folder 391)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 392)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 393)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 394)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1968 (Box 59, Folder 395)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 396)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 397)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 398)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 399)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 400)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 401)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 402)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 403)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 404)
      - Reports (Printed) - Progress Report, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 405)
    - Indian Agricultural Program - Crop Improvement Programs - Seed Development, 1959-1973, n.d.; I4.04
      Correspondence relating to the establishment and organization of the seed development program appears first within this subseries. Correspondence of a miscellaneous character follows, treating such technical matters as experiment station operations, equipment maintenance, conference and workshop scheduling, training programs, relations with other agricultural organizations, and research programs in seed collection, breeding, entomology and pathology.
      Correspondence is typically followed by unpublished and published reports summarizing the results of experimental tests. These reports are arranged alphabetically by title. Filed with unpublished reports are manuscript drafts of reports on various aspects of the research programs. Also present are "trip reports" written by staff from the field. This subseries has trip reports by Wayne H. Freeman, A. A. Johnson, B. L. Renfro, Ernest W. Sprague, and Jack Dee Traywick.
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1959-May 1962 (Box 62, Folder 406)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1959-May 1962 (Box 62, Folder 407)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1959-May 1962 (Box 62, Folder 408)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1959-May 1962 (Box 62, Folder 409)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1959-May 1962 (Box 62, Folder 410)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1959-May 1962 (Box 62, Folder 411)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1959-May 1962 (Box 62, Folder 412)
      - Correspondence - Administration, June 1962-August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 413)
      - Correspondence - Administration, June 1962-August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 414)
      - Correspondence - Administration, June 1962-August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 415)
      - Correspondence - Administration, June 1962-August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 416)
      - Correspondence - Administration, June 1962-August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 417)
      - Correspondence - Administration, June 1962-August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 418)
      - Correspondence - Administration, June 1962-August 1965 (Box 63, Folder 419)
      - Correspondence - Administration, September 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 420)
      - Correspondence - Administration, September 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 421)
      - Correspondence - Administration, September 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 422)
      - Correspondence - Administration, September 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 423)
      - Correspondence - Administration, September 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 424)
      - Correspondence - Administration, September 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 425)
      - Correspondence - Administration, September 1965-1970 (Box 64, Folder 426)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1971-1973 (Box 65, Folder 427)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1971-1973 (Box 65, Folder 428)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1971-1973 (Box 65, Folder 429)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1971-1973 (Box 65, Folder 430)
      - Correspondence - Certification and Regulations, 1959-1968 (Box 65, Folder 431)
      - Correspondence - India Crop Improvement and Certified Seed Producers' Association, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 432)
      - Correspondence - Indian Council of Agricultural Research Action Committee on Seed Development, 1959-1961 (Box 65, Folder 433)
      - Correspondence - National Seeds Corporation, No date (Box 65, Folder 434)
      - Correspondence - National Tonnage Club of Farmers, 1965-1968 (Box 65, Folder 435)
      - Correspondence - Training Programs, 1964-1968 (Box 66, Folder 436)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - Seed Reports and Attachments, 1960-1964, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 437)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - Seed Reports and Attachments, 1960-1964, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 438)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - Seed Reports and Attachments, 1960-1964, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 439)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - Trip Reports - Freeman, Wayne H., September 1961-October 1965, January 1967 (Box 66, Folder 440)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - Trip Reports - Johnson, A. A., October 1960-April 1961 (Box 66, Folder 441)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - Trip Reports - Renfro, B. L., August-September 1961 (Box 66, Folder 442)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - Trip Reports - Sprague, Ernest W., July-August 1961 (Box 66, Folder 443)
      - Reports (Manuscript) - Trip Reports - Traywick, Jack Dee, September 1961-September 1964 (Box 66, Folder 444)
      - Reports (Printed) - All India Seed Testing Workshop Proceedings, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 445)
      - Reports (Printed) - Improved Agricultural Seeds, 1960, 1962; 2 volumes (Box 67, Folder 446)
      - Reports (Printed) - The Lebanese Seed Program (Draft), 1972 (Box 67, Folder 447)
      - Reports (Printed) - Proceedings - First All India Symposium on Improved Seed Equipment, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 448)
      - Reports (Printed) - Proceedings of Seed Specialists' Seminar, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 449)
      - Reports (Printed) - Proceedings - Seed Improvement Training Courses - Volume 1, 1965-1966 (Box 68, Folder 450)
      - Reports (Printed) - Proceedings - Seed Improvement Training Courses - Volume 2, 1965-1966 (Box 69, Folder 451)
      - Reports (Printed) - Seed Certification Manual, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 452)
      - Reports (Printed) - Seed Improvement in India, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 453)
      - Reports (Printed) - Seed Processing, Storage, and Distribution Manual, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 454)
      - Reports (Printed) - Seed Production Manual, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 455)
      - Reports (Printed) - Seed Review Team Report, 1968 (Box 70, Folder 456)
      - Seed Monographs - Field Inspection Manual, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 457)
      - Seed Monographs - A Handbook for Seed Inspectors, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 458)
      - Seed Monographs - Indian Minimum Seed Certification Standards, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 459)
      - Seed Monographs - Seed Marketing, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 460)
      - Seed Monographs, 1970, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 461)
        Seed Processing, 1970 Seed Processing Plant Operator's Handbook, 1972
      - Seed Monographs - Seed Storage and Packaging - Applications for India, 1970 (Box 71, Folder 462)
      - Seed Monographs - Seed Testing Manual, 1967 (Box 71, Folder 463)
    - Indian Agricultural Program - Crop Improvement Programs - Sorghum, 1957-1973, n.d.; I4.05
      Correspondence relating to the establishment and organization of the sorghum program appears first within this subseries. Correspondence of a miscellaneous character follows, treating such technical matters as experiment station operations, equipment maintenance, conference and workshop scheduling, training programs, relations with other agricultural organizations, and research programs in seed collection, breeding, entomology and pathology.
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1969 (Box 72, Folder 464)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1969 (Box 72, Folder 465)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1969 (Box 72, Folder 466)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1969 (Box 72, Folder 467)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1969 (Box 72, Folder 468)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1969 (Box 72, Folder 469)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1969 (Box 72, Folder 470)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1957-1969 (Box 72, Folder 471)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1970-1973 (Box 73, Folder 472)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1970-1973 (Box 73, Folder 473)
      - Correspondence - Administration, 1970-1973 (Box 73, Folder 474)
      - Correspondence - Bibliography of Sorghum Literature, 1964-1970 (Box 73, Folder 475)
      - Correspondence - "Sorghum: A Bibliogaphy of the World Literature, 1964-69", 1964-1969 (Box 73, Folder 476)
        Manuscript.
      - Correspondence - Breeders' Conference, 1960-1964 (Box 73, Folder 477)
      - Correspondence - Cooperating Agencies and Stations, 1957-1964 (Box 73, Folder 478)
      - Correspondence - Equipment and Supplies, 1957-1965 (Box 73, Folder 479)
      - Correspondence - Equipment and Supplies, 1970-1971 (Box 74, Folder 480)
      - Correspondence - Experiment Stations - Coimbatore, 1962-1968 (Box 74, Folder 481)
      - Correspondence - Experiment Stations - Hyderabad, 1960-1972 (Box 74, Folder 482)
      - Correspondence - Experiment Stations - Kota, 1959-1960 (Box 74, Folder 483)
      - Correspondence - Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations - Training Program at IARI, 1970-1971 (Box 74, Folder 484)
      - Correspondence - Germplasm Collection Program, 1957-1967 (Box 74, Folder 485)
      - Correspondence - Germplasm Collection Program, 1957-1967 (Box 74, Folder 486)
      - Correspondence - Germplasm Collection Program, 1957-1967 (Box 74, Folder 487)
      - Correspondence - International Sorghum and Millets Project, 1965-1967 (Box 74, Folder 488)
      - Correspondence - International Sorghum and Millets Project, 1968-1971 (Box 75, Folder 489)